Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records 5149
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- I.C.C.- Cars Using Sub-Standard Brakes, as Complained of by Members of Lodge #231 (Box 140, Folder 17)
- B.&O. R.R.- Removal of Signals (Box 140, Folder 18)
- Erie & D.L.W. R.R.'s- Proposed Merger Finance Docket 20707 (Box 140, Folder 19)
- Erie-Lackawanna R.R.- F.D. 21671 Abandon Portion of Scranton Div. (5.67 Miles) Between Pittston Township and Plains Township (Box 140, Folder 20)
- DOT/FRA/ICC Railroad Accident Investigations (Box 140, Folder 21)
  Pamphlet-sized documents
- ICC Railroad Accident Investigations I (Box 140, Folder 22)
- ICC Railroad Accident Investigations II (Box 140, Folder 23)
  Letter-sized reports
- I.C.C. (Reports-Accident) OTHER (Box 140, Folder 24)
- ICC Letters (1946-1950) (Box 141, Folder 1)
- ICC Letters (1951) (Box 141, Folder 2)
- ICC: Letters (1952-1954) (Box 141, Folder 3)
- ICC: Letters (1954-1955) (Box 141, Folder 4)
- ICC: Letters (1956-1957) (Box 141, Folder 5)
- ICC: Letters (1958-1959) (Box 141, Folder 6)
- Booklets (Box 141, Folder 7)
- B.&L.E. R.R. & Unity R.R.- Authority to Provide Locomotive Power and Crews to Move Empty and/or Loaded Cars Over Unity Railways Line of Railroad, Located in Alleghany County (Lodge #435) (Box 142, Folder 1)
- B.&L.E. R.R.- Condition of Cobra Brake Shoes and Hand Brakes (Lodge #435) (Box 142, Folder 2)
- Public Notices and Orders (Box 142, Folder 3)
- B.&O. R.R.- Proposed Amendments F.D. 23350 (Box 142, Folder 4)
- B.&O. R.R.- Radio Communications BS-Ap-No. 15599 (Box 142, Folder 5)
- B.&O. R.R.- Unsafe Operating Practices at East Side Yard, Phila., Pa. (Lodge #953) (Box 142, Folder 6)
- Cornwall R.R. Proposed Abandonment between Cornwall-Mt. Hope, Pa.-6.4 Mi. (F.D. No. 23021)/Reading R.R.- Lease all of Cornwall R.R. After Abandonment Between Cornwall-Mt. Hope, Pa. (F.D. No. 23022) (Box 142, Folder 7)
- C.R.R. of N.J. Reading. Co. Lehigh Coal & Navigation Co.- Consolidate the Allentown Yard with the Reading & Lehigh Valley (F.D. 23151-23156) (Box 142, Folder 8)
- Erie-Lack. R.R.- Sharon Steel Corp. Using E.L. R.R. Track in Ohio at Auto Baling Co. (Lodge 521) (Box 142, Folder 9)
- Lehigh & New England & Erie-Lackawanna R.R.- BS-Ap-No. 15352: Discontinuance of Dexter Hill Interlocking system on the Bangor & Portland Branch of the Erie-Lack. R.R. at Nazareth, Pa. (Box 142, Folder 10)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- Abandon Trackage Hazleton Branch- 18.6 mi., Main and Side Tracks (Box 142, Folder 11)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- Abandonment of Portion of Bowman Creek Branch from Milepost 181.250 at Luzerne to Milepost 187.513 at Dallas, Luzerne County (Lodge #189) (Box 142, Folder 12)
- Monongahela Connecting R.R.- Civil Action No.64-836: Discontinuance of Interlocking (29th Street Tower) (Box 142, Folder 13)
- New York Central R.R. & Beech Creek R.R.- Abandonment of Trackage Bald Eagle Jct. to Snow Shoe (F.D. 23721) (Box 142, Folder 14)
- Norfolk & Western R.R.- Unprotected Spurs in CTC Territory (Lodge #259) (Box 142, Folder 15)
- Penna. R.R.- Air Brake Inspection (Lodge #742) (Box 142, Folder 16)
- Penna. R.R.- Condition of "ABD" or Cobra-Type Brakes (Lodge #574) (Box 142, Folder 17)
- Penna. R.R.- Discontinuance of Interlocking and Block Station, Etc. (Lodge #444) BS-AP-No. 15582 (Box 142, Folder 18)
- Penna. R.R.- Handling of Hydrocyanic Acid (Lodge #946) (Box 142, Folder 19)
- Penna. R.R.- Hopper Cars (Lodge #345) (Box 142, Folder 20)
- P.R.R.- Operating Practices (Lodge #63) (Box 142, Folder 21)
- Penna. R.R.- Wreck Train (Lodge #258) (Box 142, Folder 22)
- Phila., Beth. & New England R.R.- Hazardous Condition of Rolling Stock at Bethlehem Steel Corp. (Lodge #989) (Box 142, Folder 23)
- Union R.R.- Modifications of Interlockings, "MO" Tower, Bessemer, "J" Tower, Duquesne, "BR" Tower, Bull Run, and Munhall, Pa. BS-Ap-No. 15444 (Box 142, Folder 24)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- Discontinuance of Service-All Passenger Operations (F.D. 20443) (Box 142, Folder 25)
- Montour R.R.- Violation of Power Brake Law (Box 142, Folder 26)
- N.Y.C. R.R.- FD 21204-21206: Merger Material (Box 142, Folder 27)
- N.Y.C. R.R.- Violation of Safety Appliance Act (Power Brake Law)- Avis, Pa. (Lodge #344) (Box 142, Folder 28)
- New York, Chicago, & St. Louis R.R. and Norfolk & Western Rwy. -Merge, Purchase, and Lease Other Properties (Box 142, Folder 29)
- P.&L.E. R.R.- CH Interlocking Plant- Air Brakes (Box 142, Folder 30)
- P.&L.E. R.R.- Lack of Running Boards on Certain of Its Cars (Box 142, Folder 31)
- Proposed Lake Erie- Ohio River Canal (Box 142, Folder 32)
- P.R.R.- Defective Air Brakes (Lodge #42) (Box 142, Folder 33)
- P.R.R.- Defective Air Brakes (Lodge #742) (Box 142, Folder 34)
- P.R.R.- Defective Center Sill on Cars Between Conway, Conemaugh, & Altoona (Lodge #498) (Box 142, Folder 35)
- P.R.R.- Defective Handbrakes (Erie-Hammermill Paper Co.) Lodge #199 (Box 142, Folder 36)
- P.R.R.- Defective Pullman Car- "Juniper Falls" (Box 142, Folder 37)
- P.R.R.- Inoperative Air Brake- Car G.A.C.X. 43893, Train WC-11 (Lodge #571) (Box 142, Folder 38)
- P.R.R.- Loading Stock Out of the Chicago Union Stock Yard (Box 142, Folder 39)
- P.R.R.- Finance Docket 21459: To Acquire Control of the Lehigh Valley Railroad Through Stock Ownership (Box 142, Folder 40)
- P.R.R.- Violation of Power Brake Law (Lodge #105) (Box 142, Folder 41)
- P.R.R.- Violation of Safety Appliance Act (Lodge #292) (Box 142, Folder 42)
- Reading R.R.- F.D. 21882: Trackage Right Over P.R.R.-P.R.S.L. Phila.- Camden, N.J. (Box 142, Folder 43)
- Reading R.R.- Violation of Safety Appliance Act- Hand Brakes on Certain Cars (Box 142, Folder 44)
- Southern Pacific Company- FD 20444: Partial Discontinuance Between Calif. And Oregon. (Box 142, Folder 45)
- Union R.R.- I.C.C. 15200: Discontinuance of Block Signals (Box 142, Folder 46)
- Various Railroads- Drawbar Extensions on Pullman-Standard Hydroframe-60 Box Cars (Box 142, Folder 47)
- Statements (Box 142, Folder 48)
- Philadelphia Regional Meeting (Box 142, Folder 49)
- Pittsburgh Regional Meeting (Box 142, Folder 50)
- Ruder & Finn, Inc. (Box 142, Folder 51)
- Pennsylvania Committee to Preserve Railroad Service (Bank Account) (Box 142, Folder 52)
- B.&O. R.R. and P.&L.E. R.R.- A.85826- A.85765-85788: Discontinuance of Passenger Trains Between Ellwood City and Wampum, Lawrence County. (Box 143, Folder 1)
- B.&O. R.R.- C#63-472, F.D. 22201: Discontinuance of Passenger Trains Nos. 21 & 22, Baltimore-Washington-Pittsburgh. (Box 143, Folder 2)
- B.&O. R.R.- F.D. 21958: Discontinuance of Trains Nos. 17 and 18 (Box 143, Folder 3)
- B.&O. R.R.- Discontinuance of Trains #3 & #4- "The Diplomat"-Between Baltimore, Md. & St. Louis, Mo., 1960 (Box 143, Folder 4)
- B.&O. R.R.- Extensive Cut in Passenger Train Service Between Washington and New York (Box 143, Folder 5)
- B.&O. R.R. & Reading. Co.-Removal of Passenger Train Serv. Between Baltimore, Md. & Jersey City, N.J. (Box 143, Folder 6)
- B.&O. R.R. and Reading. R.R.- Abandonment of Passenger Train Service Between Chester, and the 24th & Chestnut Sts. And Wayne Junction Stations, Philadelphia. (Box 143, Folder 7)
- Chesapeake & Ohio RR: Discontinuance of Passenger Trains Nos. 46 and 47 (Box 143, Folder 8)
- C.R.R. of N.J.- Discontinuance of Passenger Trains. Nos. 301 & 306 Between Jim Thorpe and Wilkes-Barre (Box 143, Folder 9)
- D.L.&W. R.R.- Trains 26, 28, and 11: Hoboken N.J. & Scranton (Box 143, Folder 10)
- Erie-Lackawanna R.R.- Discontinuance of Trains L-5 and L-2 (Box 143, Folder 11)
- Erie-Lack. R.R.- Discontinuance of Trains Nos. 25 & 26, 41 & 43 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  FD 22551 and 22552
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- Abandonment all Pass. Trains Between City of Hazleton, Luz. Co. & Lehighton, Carbon Co. (A. 86035) (Box 143, Folder 13)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- I.C.C. and P.U.C 51: Discontinuance of Passenger Train Service (Box 143, Folder 14)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- F.D. 20824: Discontinuance of Trains 228, 229, 239, & 207 (Hazleton-Lehighton) (Box 143, Folder 15)
- N.Y., C&S.L. R.R.- Discontinuance of Trains Nos. 7 & 8 Between Buffalo, N.Y. and Chicago, Ill. (Box 143, Folder 16)
- Penna. R.R.- Abandonment of Service on Cumberland Valley Branch, by Discontinuance of Train Nos. 638 and 645, Between Harrisburg and Pa.-Md. Boundary Line (Box 143, Folder 17)
  FD 21936 A89818
- Penna. R.R.- Approval of Discontinuance of Pass. Trains #0765 & 0768, Between Media & W. Chester) (Box 143, Folder 18)
  A. 85815
- Penna. R.R.- Curtailment of Passenger Trains- Lodges #511 & #574 (Box 143, Folder 19)
- Penna. R.R.- Discontinuance of Passenger Train #363, Between Pittsburgh & Beaver A. 85491 (Box 143, Folder 20)
- Penna. R.R.- Discontinuance of Pass. Trains Nos. 64 and 65, Between Pgh. And Beaver Falls (775, 345, 1010) A. 85641 (Box 143, Folder 21)
- Penna. R.R.- Discontinuance of Passenger Trains Nos. 807 & 810 Between Pittsburgh & Elrama Station A. 89906 (Box 143, Folder 22)
- Penna. R.R.- Discontinuance of Passenger Trains 38, 40, 41, and 54 (Box 143, Folder 23)
- Penna. R.R. -Discontinuance of Thirty Passenger Trains Which Would Result in Abandonment of All Suburban Passenger Train Service in the Pittsburgh Area. CA 61-398, FD 21589, A. 87747 (Box 143, Folder 24)
- Penna. R.R.- Discontinuance of Trains #570, #576, #572, #571, #573, Buffalo, NY & Harrisburg, PA (Box 143, Folder 25)
- Penna. R.R.- Discontinuance of Trains #528 and #529- Harrisburg & Williamsport ICC FD 20792, A. 85497 (Box 143, Folder 26)
- Penna. R.R.- Discontinuance of Trains #45, Operated Sundays Only, Between Scranton, Pa. and Binghamton, N.Y. (Lodge #95) (Box 143, Folder 27)
- Penna. R.R.- Discontinuance of Train #26 (Pgh. To Hbg.) A. 87361 (Box 143, Folder 28)
- Penna. R.R.- Hyde Park Foundry (Box 144, Folder 1)
- Penna. R.R.- Improper Equipment (Lack of Fuses & Torpedoes- Lodge #574) (Box 144, Folder 2)
- Penna. R.R.- Improper Flagging Equipment for Rear-End of Passenger Trains (Lodge #299) (Box 144, Folder 3)
- Penna. R.R.- Improper Flagging Equipment for Rear-End of Passenger Trains (Lodge #574) (Box 144, Folder 4)
- Penna. R.R.- Improper Flagging Equipment for Rear-End of Passenger Trains (Lodge #753) (Box 144, Folder 5)
- Penna. R.R.- Improper Flagging Equipment for Rear-End of Freight Trains (Lodge #753) (Box 144, Folder 6)
- Penna. R.R.- Installation of Lights at Stoney Creek Yard, Thurlow District- Lodge #488 (Box 144, Folder 7)
- Penna. R.R.- Installation of Lights at Wheatland Yard (Lodge #521) C. 17170 (Box 144, Folder 8)
- Penna. R.R.- Interlocking Switch at Kiski Yards- Lodge #753 (Box 144, Folder 9)
- Penna. R.R.- Lack of Inspection of Cars- Blairsville & Kiski Jct. (Box 144, Folder 10)
- Penna. R.R.- Liberty-Crosstown Thoroughfare A. 84094 (Box 144, Folder 11)
- Penna. R.R.- Locking of Stations at Ardmore, Bryn Mawr & Strafford and Train #16 (Box 144, Folder 12)
- Penna. R.R.- Monongahela Dist., Pgh. Region, Unsafe Conditions I.D. 37 (Box 144, Folder 13)
- Penna. R.R.- Operation of Train #549 (Lodge #1021) (Box 144, Folder 14)
- Penna. R.R.- Operation of Trains Nos. 361 and 39 (Lodge #511) (Box 144, Folder 15)
- Penna. R.R.- Overhead Ramp at Leechburg Station (Box 144, Folder 16)
- Penna. R.R.- Passenger Platform at Middletown Station (Box 144, Folder 17)
- Penna. R.R.- Penn Iron and Steel Company, Pittsburgh, Pa.- Unsafe Conditions (Box 144, Folder 18)
- Penna. R.R.- Pgh. Region, Conemaugh District, Between Kiski-Jct. and Phillipston, Penna. (Box 144, Folder 19)
- Penna. R.R.- P.I. Division-Unsafe Interlocking Lodge #160 (Box 144, Folder 20)
- Penna. R.R.- P.U.C. (Poor Equipment, People Standing, and Cleaning-up of Passenger Trains) (Box 144, Folder 21)
- Penna. R.R.- Removal of Front Brakeman From Trains #28, #29, #60, & #61 (Lodges #574 & #775) (Box 144, Folder 22)
- Penna. R.R.- Ramp Being Constructed at Lykens for Loading Coal From Trucks Into Open Top Railroad Cars (Box 144, Folder 23)
- Penna. R.R.- Rosston Bridge #753- Fullerton Powell Coal Co.; Elier Pottery #258- Rettig Bostonia Bridge (Box 144, Folder 24)
- Penna. R.R.- Rule #19 (Box 144, Folder 25)
- Penna. R.R.- Swing Brakeman, Doc. 13455 (Box 144, Folder 26)
- Penna. R.R.- Swing Brakeman (Box 144, Folder 27)
- Penna. R.R.- Switch- Conway Yard (Lodge #299) (Box 144, Folder 28)
- Penna. R.R.- Switches (Box 144, Folder 29)
- Penna. R.R.- Switches & Weeds (Lodge #299) (Box 144, Folder 30)
- Penna. R.R.- T-1 Crew Removal of Brakeman (Lodge #105) (Box 144, Folder 31)
- Penna. R.R.- T-3 Crew Removal of Brakeman (Lodge #105) C. 17074 (Box 144, Folder 32)
- Penna. R.R.- Train Wreck (Steelton, Pa.) I.D. 66 (Box 144, Folder 33)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe and Hazardous Conditions at Southbound Yard- Thurlow Hump- Chester, Pa. (Lodge #488) (Box 144, Folder 34)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe and Hazardous Conditions in the Shire Oaks-Brownsville Area and Redstone Secondary Track (Lodges #299 & #461) (Box 144, Folder 35)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions at Hbg. Station, Caused by Pigeons (Box 144, Folder 36)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions at Renovo, Pa. (Lodge #338) (Box 144, Folder 37)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions in Lancaster Area- Lodge #117 (Box 144, Folder 38)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions- Lodge #498 (Box 144, Folder 39)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe & Unsanitary Conditions (Lodge #948- Munhall Yard., Thomson Yd. and Shire Oaks) (Box 144, Folder 40)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Condition at Altoona Passenger Station- Train Shed (Lodge #775) (Box 144, Folder 41)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Condition at Rose Tower, Juniata, Altoona, Pa. (Lodges #174 & #498); C. 17738 (Box 144, Folder 42)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions- Gallitzin to Altoona- Eastern Slope (Lodge #498) (Box 144, Folder 43)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions Relative to Open Hopper Doors Over Public & Private Crossings (Lodge #521) (Box 144, Folder 44)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions and Weeds Phila. Terminal Div.- Lodge #160 (Box 144, Folder 45)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions at New Castle Jct. (Lodge #955) (Box 144, Folder 46)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions at Pittsburgh, Pa. (Lodge #299) (Box 144, Folder 47)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions at Pittsburgh Passenger Yard (Lodge #309) (Box 144, Folder 48)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions at Sharpsburg and Herr's Island Terminal (Lodge #467) (Box 144, Folder 49)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions at Station Building, 52nd Street, Phila. (Lodge #511) (Box 144, Folder 50)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions Caused by Weeds & Debris, on the Monon. Dist., Pgh. Region, P.R.R. (Lodge #948) (Box 144, Folder 51)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions in Scully District (Lodge #571) (Box 144, Folder 52)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions in the Cresson, Pa. Area (Mulvihill) (Box 144, Folder 53)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions on Commuter Stations on Main Line (Lodge #511) (Box 144, Folder 54)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions- Weeds in Woodvale Yard & South Fork Branch- Lodge #386 (Box 144, Folder 55)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsanitary Conditions at Conway Yard (B.R.C.) (Box 144, Folder 56)
- Penna. R.R.- Various Hazardous Conditions in the Philadelphia Area (Lodge #160) (Box 144, Folder 57)
- Penna. R.R.- Various Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions- Lodges #258, #753 (Box 144, Folder 58)
- Penna. R.R.- Weeds & Debris at Various Yards & Sidings- Lodge #467 (Box 144, Folder 59)
- Penna. R.R.- Weeds and Inadequate Lighting at Moravia Yard (Lodge #955) (Box 144, Folder 60)
- Penna. R.R.- Weeds and Trees at McClay St. in Harrisburg (Lodge #383) (Box 144, Folder 61)
- Penna. R.R.- Weeds, Trees, and Debris on Various Slidings Between Springdale & Blawnox (Lodge #467) (Box 144, Folder 62)
- Penna. R.R.- Wire Train Crews Operating Out of Lancaster- Lodge #117 (Box 144, Folder 63)
- Penna. R.R. and Reading R.R.- Commuter Fare Increases (Lodges #511 & #978); C. 17412 & C. 17413 (Box 144, Folder 64)
- P.R.R. and W. Maryland R.R.- Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions at D.E. Horn Co., York and P.H. Gladfelter Co., Spring Grove- Lodge #1021 (Box 144, Folder 65)
- P.&L.E. R.R.- Application for Exemption from Part III of Commission's Railroad Regulations at McKees Rocks Yard, Allegheny County; A. 88592 (Box 144, Folder 66)
- P.&L.E. R.R.- Discontinuance of Less Than Carload Freight Service at All Stations on its Main Line, Ohio River Branch, Etc. (Box 144, Folder 67)
- P.&L.E. R.R.- Discontinuance of Less-Than-Carload Freight Service (Youghiogheny Div.- Monongahela) #86784 (Box 144, Folder 68)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie R.R.- Lack of Heat in Station Office Bldgs. & Waiting Rms. -Lodge #231 (Box 144, Folder 69)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie R.R.- Neville Island Branch Bridge; A. 85043 (Box 144, Folder 70)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie R.R.- Unsafe Conditions- Walkways on Cedar Street Bridge, Weeds & Debris, Etc. (Box 144, Folder 71)
- Pittsburgh & Shawmut R.R.- Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions (Lodge #573) (Box 144, Folder 72)
- Proposed Methods of Railroad Exhibits in Passenger Train Discontinuances (Box 144, Folder 73)
- Railway Express Agency, Inc.- Abandonment of Its Agency- Boro. Of Shenandoah, Schuyl. Co.; A. 87016 (Box 144, Folder 74)
- Reading R.R.- Change in Status of Fox Chase Sta. Located Rhawn St.-56th Ward-Phila.; A. 86669 (Box 144, Folder 75)
- Reading R.R.- Approval of the Abandonment of Service on Sidetrack; A. 91658 (Box 144, Folder 76)
- Reading R.R.- Change in Status of Station at Borough of Bridgeport; A. 88271 (Box 144, Folder 77)
- Reading R.R.- Change in Status of Station at Mount Carmel; A. 87136 (Box 144, Folder 78)
- Reading R.R.- Change in Status of Station Boro. Of Frackville-Schuylkill County; A. 88392 (Box 144, Folder 79)
- Reading R.R.- Change in Status of Station at Yardley; A. 86770 (Box 144, Folder 80)
- Reading R.R.- Change in Status of Station in Reading, Berks Cty.; A. 90569 (Box 144, Folder 81)
- Reading R.R.- Change in Status of Station Wycombe (Bucks County); A. 86771 (Box 144, Folder 82)
- B.&O. and Reading R.R.- Phila. Terminal Cases-Lodge #953 (Box 144, Folder 83)
- Rhode Island Legis. Board (Box 145, Folder 1)
- Rhode Island Legis. Board, 1963-1966 (Box 145, Folder 2)
- South Carolina Legis. Board, 1963-1966 (Box 145, Folder 3)
- South Dakota Congressional Endorsements, 1965-1966 (Box 145, Folder 4)
- South Dakota Legislative Rep., 1965 (Box 145, Folder 5)
- South Dakota Legislative Rep. (Box 145, Folder 6)
- South Dakota Legis. Board (Box 145, Folder 7)
- Tennessee Legis. Board, 1963-1964 (Box 145, Folder 8)
- Texas Legis. Board, 1963-1965 (Box 145, Folder 9)
- Texas Legis. Board, 1965-1966 (Box 145, Folder 10)
- Texas Legis. Board, 1963-1964 (Box 145, Folder 11)
- Texas Legis. Board, 1965-1966 (Box 145, Folder 12)
- Utah State Legis. Board (Box 145, Folder 13)
- Utah State Legis. Board (Box 145, Folder 14)
- Vermont State Legis. Board, 1965-1966 (Box 145, Folder 15)
- Vermont State Legis. Board, 1963-1964 (Box 145, Folder 16)
- Virginia State Legis. Board (Box 145, Folder 17)
- Virginia State Legis. Board (Box 145, Folder 18)
- Washington State Legis. Board (Box 145, Folder 19)
- Washington State Legis. Boards (Box 145, Folder 20)
- West Virginia State Legislative Board (Box 145, Folder 21)
- West Virginia State Legis. Board (Box 145, Folder 22)
- Wisconsin State Legis. Board (Box 145, Folder 23)
- Wisconsin State Legis. Board (Box 145, Folder 24)
- Wyoming State Legis. Board (Box 145, Folder 25)
- Wyoming State Legis. Boards (Box 145, Folder 26)
- Wyoming State Legis. Boards (Box 145, Folder 27)
- NJ/Penn RR & Shore Line RR, 1963-1966 (Box 145, Folder 28)
- NJ/Reading RR Co., 1962-1968 (Box 145, Folder 29)
- General State Legislature Material (Box 145, Folder 30)
- Nat'l Conference of State Legislative Representatives (Canadian), 1958 (Box 145, Folder 31)
- Midwest Assoc. of State Legis. Representatives, 1964-1968 (Box 145, Folder 32)
- New England Assoc. of State Legis. Representatives, 1965-1968 (Box 145, Folder 33)
- Western Conf. of State Legis. Representative., 1965-1968 (Box 145, Folder 34)
- S.E. Assoc. of State Legis. Representative. (Box 145, Folder 35)
- Nat'l Assoc. of State Leg. Representatives: Great Lakes Region, 1965-1968 (Box 145, Folder 36)
- Correspondence With Various State Legis. Bds., 1965-1968 (Box 145, Folder 37)
- Nat'l Conference of State Legislative Representatives, 1966 (Box 145, Folder 38)
- Nat'l Conference of State Legis. Reports, 1962-1964 (Box 145, Folder 39)
- Nat'l Conference of State Legislative Representatives, 1960 (Box 145, Folder 40)
- Akron, Canton, & Youngstown Ry. (Box 146, Folder 1)
- The Akron & Barbeton Belt R.R. (Box 146, Folder 2)
- Alabama Great Southern Railroad (Now Under Southern RR. West), 1917-1929 (Box 146, Folder 3)
- Alaska Railroad Company (Box 146, Folder 4)
  Unfoldered; It is a bundle of three stapled papers.
- Atlanta & West Point Railroad: The Western Railway of Alabama, 1911-1922 (Box 146, Folder 5)
- Atlanta & St. Andrews Bay R.R., 1937-1944 (Box 146, Folder 6)
- Atlanta & St. Andrews Bay Railway (Box 146, Folder 7)
  Unfoldered, but is tied with a rubber band.
- Atlanta, Birmingham & Coast Railroad Co. (Box 146, Folder 8)
- Atlanta, Birmingham & Coast RR. (Box 146, Folder 9)
- Atlanta Joint Terminals (Box 146, Folder 10)
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe (Coast Lines) (1) (Box 146, Folder 11)
  One of six. Label was ripped when retrieved.
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe (Coast Lines) (2) (Box 146, Folder 12)
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe (Coast Lines) (3) (Box 146, Folder 13)
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe (Coast Lines) (4) (Box 146, Folder 14)
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe (Coast Lines) (5) (Box 146, Folder 15)
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Ry. Co. (Coast Lines) (6) (Box 146, Folder 16)
- Baltimore & Eastern (BS & A and MD &V) (Box 146, Folder 17)
- Baltimore & Ohio R.R. (1) (Box 146, Folder 18)
- Baltimore & Ohio R.R. (2) (Box 146, Folder 19)
- Alameda (Cal.) Belt Line R.R. (Owned by AT&SF and W.P.) (Box 147, Folder 1)
- The Alaska Railroad (Box 147, Folder 2)
- Albany & Hudson Railroad (Box 147, Folder 3)
- Albany Port District Commission R.R. (Box 147, Folder 4)
- Algoma Central & Hudson Bay Ry. (Box 147, Folder 5)
- Algoma Eastern Ry. Co. (Box 147, Folder 6)
- Algoma Eastern Railway (Box 147, Folder 7)
- Algoma Steel Corporation Limited (Box 147, Folder 8)
- Aliquippa. & So. (Box 147, Folder 9)
  No folder.
- Allegheny and South Side Railway Co. (Box 147, Folder 10)
- Alabama, Tennessee & Northern Ry. (Box 147, Folder 11)
- Alton Railroad, Co. (Box 147, Folder 12)
- Alton & Southern Railroad (Box 147, Folder 13)
- Alton and Southern Railroad (Box 147, Folder 14)
  Unfoldered, held together by a rubber band
- Aliquippa and Southern Railroad Company (Box 147, Folder 15)
  Blue booklet.
- Ann Arbor Railroad Company (Box 147, Folder 16)
  Unfoldered.
- Ann Arbor Railroad Company, 1901-1929 (Box 147, Folder 17)
- Anniston Warehouse Corporation, 1944 (Box 147, Folder 18)
- Apache Railway Co., 1939 (Box 147, Folder 19)
- Apache Railway Co., 1958 (Box 147, Folder 20)
- Arizona & New Mexico Railway (Box 147, Folder 21)
- Arkansas & Louisiana Missouri Ry. (Box 147, Folder 22)
- Aroostook Valley Railroad Company (Box 147, Folder 23)
  Unfoldered
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe (1) (Coast Lines) (Box 147, Folder 24)
- Atlantic & Yadkin Railway, 1919 (Box 147, Folder 25)
- Atlantic & East Carolina Ry. Co. (Box 147, Folder 26)
- Atlantic Coast Line (Box 147, Folder 27)
- Atlantic Coast Line (Box 147, Folder 28)
- Barre and Chelsea Railroad Co. (Box 148, Folder 1)
- Bellingham Bay & British Columbia Railroad Company (Box 148, Folder 2)
- Bellingham & Northern Railway Co. (Box 148, Folder 3)
- Belt Railway of Chicago (Box 148, Folder 4)
- Buffalo Creek Railroad (Box 148, Folder 5)
- Buffalo and Susquehanna (Box 148, Folder 6)
- Brown Shipbuilding Company (Box 148, Folder 7)
- Barre & Chelsea Railroad (Box 148, Folder 8)
- Buffalo Creek & Gauley Railroad Co. (Box 148, Folder 9)
- Burlington-Rock Island (Box 148, Folder 10)
- Bangor & Aroostook R.R. (Box 148, Folder 11)
- Baltimore & Ohio R.R. Co. (Box 148, Folder 12)